usell.com 2013-04-30

# uSell Privacy Policy | uSell

This Privacy Policy describes how uSell.com ("we" or "us") gathers and uses personal information submitted on our website www.uSell.com (uSell.com). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

uSell.com searches the web for the best offers to trade in or recycle your old electronics; then uSell.com refers you to a reseller or recycler's website to sell or recycle your product. uSell.com will share your personal information with these carefully selected resellers and recyclers when you agree to submit for a quote. This means we do not take your credit card information and we do not take your money. Registration on uSell.com is voluntary, if you do decide to register, we will not share your personal information until you agree to submit to a quote. You do get access to certain features if you register, but membership is not necessary to find trade-in and recycling offers.

uSell.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/index.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers the website www.uSell.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us [here](http://support.usell.com/). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

## Information We Collect

If you create a member account at the uSell.com website, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information ("PII") such as your email address. Once you register you can visit your profile on the uSell.com website at any time to add, edit or remove PII, such as your first and last name. If you decide to provide PII, you are telling us that this information is both true and accurate, and that you are authorized to provide it to us.

If you join uSell.com using a third-party social network account, such as Facebook Connect, we will collect information shared by the third-party network according to that third-party's privacy policy. In addition to the above personal information, we collect standard information about uSell.com users such as IP addresses, browser type, operating system, what you searched for, referring and exit pages, the dates and times of visits, and other site usage behavior ("Site Visitation Data"). Site Visitation Data is used to administer the site and provide general statistics regarding the use of the uSell.com website. We may also use Site Visitation Data to display advertising or send targeted email marketing messages you may find interesting and to suppress advertising that might not interest you.

To help improve our site and services, we may collect certain technical information from your browser software, screen resolution and the website that referred you to us.

## Keeping in Touch

When you choose to register with us, uSell.com logs you in automatically using your email address or Facebook profile (if you registered using Facebook Connect). This saves you the trouble of having to create and remember a log in identifier and it allows us to email you a new password should you forget your old one. If you do register with us, uSell.com will save your information and recognize you regardless of where you log in from.

uSell.com gives you the option of receiving emails from us. You can opt out of receiving these emails at any time by following the instructions located in the "Control of Personal Information" section below. Also, every email we send has an opt-out URL, so that you can unsubscribe whenever you want.

## Sharing information with friends and in user forums

The uSell.com website allows you to share certain information with friends that you select. Please bear in mind that uSell.com cannot control what your friends do with the information you share with them, so you should only share with friends you trust. Once displayed on publicly viewable web pages, information that you share can be collected and used by others. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please contact us at privacy@uSell.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Furthermore, if you participate in a user forum on the uSell.com website, your comments and your uSell.com username will be displayed to all uSell.com users on the forum. uSell.com is not responsible for what any user or third party may do with information that you choose to share.

We may also provide a feature allowing you to invite a friend to join uSell.com. If you provide a friend's email address to us for this reason, we will use that email address only for the purpose of sending a onetime invitation to your friend. Your friend may contact us at [privacy@uSell.com](mailto:%20privacy@uSell.com) to remove their information from our database.

## Use of personal information

We will treat your personal information as confidential, and we will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission, except in the limited circumstances described below.

If you accept a referral from uSell.com to one of our partner sites, we may provide PII to the partner site to save you having to re-enter that information. When you select a partner site to sell your phone to, you must opt in to allow your PII to be submitted to that partner site, and you agree to be bound by their privacy policy as regards use of your PII.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as fulfilling your request for a free shipping kit, purchasing your phone, or sending confirmation or other emails. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only _as necessary to provide_ these services to us.

We may disclose your personal information when we reasonably believe that it is required by a law or legal process and to protect and defend the rights and interests of uSell.com, its affiliates, suppliers, or users. In the event uSell.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

We may use and disclose your aggregated usage information with others, in a form that does not identify any individual, to allow uSell.com and our advertisers to present targeted advertising to you. We may disclose to third parties, including advertisers and potential business partners, aggregated statistics that we develop from your usage habits, preferences, and history. For example, we may disclose generalized information about usage habits based on aggregated statistics developed from your site usage behavior and search history. This statistical information will not identify any individual.

## Control of personal information

You can confirm, change, delete or update personal information you have provided to us by logging into your account and going to the Account Settings page, or by contacting us at [support@usell.com](mailto:%20support@usell.com).

You can change your email and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account and going to the Account Setting page and amending your email notification choices. If you wish, you can also opt-out of receiving promotional emails, by sending a request to [privacy@uSell.com](mailto:%20privacy@usell.com). When you opt-out of promotional communications from us, you may still receive service messages (such as an order confirmation) and legally mandated notices.

Please note that, even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Security of personal information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is one hundred percent secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please contact us, if you have any questions about security on our site.

## Protection of children's privacy

We do not knowingly collect any PII from people under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 is attempting to submit this information, we will inform the minor that he or she is ineligible to do so. We will then remove this information from our records.

## Use of cookies and tracking technology

When you visit our site we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more cookies. Your browser will store these cookies on your computer in a small text file, and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. For example, when you decide to log in as a uSell.com member, we store encrypted information in your browser so you don't have to log in on every page. Cookies are not linked to your personal information.

We may also use web beacons, clear gif technology, or action tags as mechanisms to collect aggregate site visitation data by tracking how users navigate to and through our website. We may also use this technology to track the delivery of HTML email messages. Data collected through this mechanism is not linked to personal information.

Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. You can enable your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may disable access to some services and tools that we offer.

uSell.com works with advertising partners to place advertising on our site. Our third party advertising partners often use a cookie or third party web beacon to track when a click becomes a sale. No PII is ever sent to these advertising partners.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

We use Java script to gather email address entered into the site. When you enter an email address onto the site, we may send periodical reminder emails to that address about items left in a cart. You may opt-out of these emails by following the unsubscribe link in an email.

## Enforcement of this policy

If you have questions about the policies described in this policy, please contact us directly using [this form](http://support.usell.com/).

## Social Media Features and Widgets

Our site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Import Contacts

You can import contacts from email account address books, to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose.

## Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## Links to other websites

We work with responsible third parties. Their business policies may include different privacy policies and practices than we have. Please be aware that when you click through to third-party websites, our privacy policies no longer apply and that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to review the policies of each site you use.

## Changes to this policy

We may from time to time update this privacy policy. When we make these updates, we will change the "last updated" date listed below. If we make a material change to this policy in how we use your personal information, we will update users by placing a more prominent notice on our home page before the change. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your use of the uSell.com website after an updated privacy policy becomes effective will indicate your acceptance of the updated policy.

## Users from outside the United States

uSell.com and the uSell.com servers are located in the United States and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of the United States. If you use the uSell.com website, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this privacy policy and subject to such laws.

## Contact information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us [here](http://support.usell.com/).

uSell.com  
200 E. Broward Blvd. Ste 1200  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301

Last Updated: 06/6/2012
